GHOFRANE BEN HMAID

Front-end developer

PROFILE:

I am a software developer with several years of experience. My expertise lies primarily in frontend development, but I also have experience developing desktop applications and back-end services.

I am a creative and responsible developer who enjoys solving problems and challenges with a positive attitude and motivation to learn new technologies.

EXPERIENCE:

Frontend Developer at Green Car Lane

Denmark Oct. 2023 - Presen

- Connect the front-end with the back-end and secure data flow.
- Develop and strengthen the back-end, database.
- Tech stack for a SaaS marketplace.
- · Work with APIs and Data Science.
- Design and develop server-side architecture.
- Test and debug software.

Frontend Developer at The Royal Danish Academy (KADK)

Denmark Sep. 2021 - Dec. 2022

· Working on developing a web application with interactive games for facial exercises, using ReactJs, NodeJS, Lottie animatione, AWS, Docker and Git. The web application was a part of an experimental project investigating into new forms of interctive physical therapy. The web app consist in a series of small games where player completes tasks by making facial expressions.

Frontend Web Developer at ADORNO

Denmark Nov. 2020 - Sep. 2021

Improving and adding features to website by WordPress.

Dotnet Developer - Bachelor Project at TopNet

Tunisia Apr. 2016 – Sep. 2016

· Final project: SQL jobs monitor (programming). Visualising the execution history of SQL Server Agent jobs in graphical mode with the possibility of real time replanning.

Photographer / Social media assistant for a member of parliament at Tunisian Parliament

Tunisia Jan. 2014 - Sep. 2016

- Management of social media accounts of member of parliament.
- · Accompanying member of parliament during all activities. Photography and video recording. Editing graphics and video. Writing and publishing articles online.

Magazine graphic designer at Bizerte News

Tunisia Okt. 2012 - Nov. 2013

· Graphic design and layout of texts and images for the whole news magazine as well as frontpage layout.

MY SKILLS:

- ✓ MongoDB
- ✓ React.js
- ✓ Node.js

- Redux Toolkit
- Context API
- ✓ CSS/SCSS
- TailwindCSS
- GSAP animation
- Media queries
- Adobes
- ✓ Figma

EDUCATION:

Full-stack web-development educational program HackYourFuture

Copenhagen Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2020

• HackYourFuture is an intensive educational program for full-stack web-development based on Javascript.

Bachelor in IT & Multimedia – Higher Institute of Multimedia Arts of Manouba

Tunisia Sep. 2011 - Jun. 2016

• Final project: SQL jobs monitor (programming). Visualising the execution history of SQL Server Agent jobs in graphical mode with the possibility of real time replanning.

VOLUNTEER WORK:

Active member in the "Mettez votre empreinte" society

• Organising various cultural events. Teaching Photoshop courses for beginners.